<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <record id="generic_request_overview"
            model="bureaucrat.knowledge.document">
        <field name="name">Generic Request Overview</field>
        <field name="category_id"
               ref="reference_generic_request_modules"/>
        <field name="document_body"><![CDATA[
                <h2>Generic Request Overview</h2>
                <p>Generic Request module is an independent application which also operates as a  part of Bureaucrat application. It is a managing system for logging, recording, tracking, addressing, handling and archiving issues that occur in daily routine.</p>
                <p>It is designed to be the single channel for submitting all the events that prevent normal business operation and saving staff desraption for asking about advise on hardware or software problems.</p>
                <p>Generic requests allows any organisation to understand own technical support requirements and define an incident managing process. The operator of the Generic Request module is responsible for following each event through its escalation process and ensure the fastest way for its resolution.</p>
                <p>Generic Request allows accumulating the information about incidents and developing knowledgebase for their quick work around, handling and resolution.</p>
                <p>All the incidents are documented and tracked until they are resolved. Information about incidents is coordinated for faster and easier resolution. Reports generated while managing the incidents allow defining the problem areas and create the ways for their preventing.</p></div>
            ]]>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="generic_request_action_hr"
            model="bureaucrat.knowledge.document">
        <field name="name">Generic Request Action (HR) Module</field>
        <field name="category_id"
               ref="reference_generic_request_modules"/>
        <field name="document_body"><![CDATA[
                <h1>Generic Request Action (HR) Module</h1>
                <p>Generic Request Action (HR) is a module developed by the Center of Research &amp; Development company. The module provides integration between the HR application and the Generic Request (Actions) module.</p>
                <p>Generic Request Action (HR) requires that the following modules and applications be installed:</p>
                <ul>
                <li>HR</li>
                <li>Generic Request (Actions)</li>
                </ul>
                <hr />
                <p>After installing the Generic Request Action (HR) module, a new assign and subscribe actions associated with the HR application are available when the request follows the route. </p>
                <p>On the form for creating action click the drop down menu <em>Type</em> and select <strong>Assign</strong> from the list. </p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/68.png" /></p>
                <p>The new <em>Assign</em> tab appears. Click on it. </p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/69.png" /></p>
                <p>Additional fields to fill will appear. Now you can make assignments to employees by position and department. To use this opportunity, the structure of the company with its employees must be configured using the HR application. </p>
                <p>For example select the Type of assignment <em>Department Employee</em>.</p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/70.png" /></p>
                <p>New fields <em>Department</em> and <em>Job</em> will appear to fill in. Additional fields will appear depending on the structure of your company.</p>
                <p>Now select the Type of action <strong>Subscribe</strong>. </p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/71.png" /></p>
                <p>In the <em>Subscribe</em> tab new drop down menu <em>Subscribe departments</em> will appear. Here you can choose the department of your company, which should sign this request to continue its promotion along the route.</p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/72.png" /></p>
                <p>For more information on creating and configuring actions, read the <a href="../Generic_Request_Actions_admin_eng/">Generic Request (Actions)</a> instruction.</p></div>
            ]]>
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="website_service_desk_field"
            model="bureaucrat.knowledge.document">
        <field name="name">Website Service Desk (Field)</field>
        <field name="category_id"
               ref="reference_website_service_desk_modules"/>
        <field name="document_body"><![CDATA[
                <h1>Website Service Desk (Field)</h1>
                <p>Website Service Desk (Field) is a module developed by the Center of Research &amp; Development company. It provides integration between the Website Service Desk and Generic Request (Fields) modules and allows to use additional fields when submitting requests using the website interface.</p>
                <p><img alt="" src="../Static/website_service_desk_31.png" /></p>
                <p>Additional fields are pre-configured by the administrator. More information on the fields setting up you can read in the instruction to the <a href="../Generic_request_fields_admin_eng/">Generic Request (Fields)</a> module.</p></div>
            ]]>
        </field>
    </record>

</odoo>
